<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheZackAZT - Web and App Developer</title>
    <description>Websites, Apps, and Technology Explained Casually.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 15:46:16 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 15:46:16 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Letter To The FCC Chairman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Ajit Pai,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You state that you are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/fcc-chair-ajit-pai-explains-wants-scrap-net-neutrality&quot;&gt;“in favor of a free and open Internet”&lt;/a&gt; for American citizens, however, your recent announcement on voting to repeal the FCC’s Open Internet Order directly contradicts any such statement of supporting a free and open Internet. Protecting Internet neutrality is absolutely vital for the American Internet to continue to grow organically. You state that the Title II regulations do more harm than good for the American people in regards to Internet access, and that without these regulations, the evolution of the Internet would then be in the hands of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politico.com/story/2017/11/22/ajit-pai-fcc-defends-net-neutrality-repeal-25816&quot;&gt;“engineers...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-letter-to-the-fcc-chairman/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-letter-to-the-fcc-chairman/</guid>
        
        
        <category>tech politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Analysis of Net Neutrality in America</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt; at the end.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Net Neutrality is a term that most people today have heard, but how much do you know about it? Should you care? Afterall, it’s not that big of a deal, right? It’s just the internet. As long as you can check your social media accounts and watch your online movies, do you think you’d be satisfied regardless?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;net-neutrality-is-not-necessarily-about-the-present&quot;&gt;Net neutrality is not necessarily about the present.&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;The thing to keep in mind here is that companies want to discriminate against certain forms of internet traffic in order to suit their business desires. The goal of net...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-analysis-of-net-neutrality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/an-analysis-of-net-neutrality/</guid>
        
        
        <category>tech politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boston Dynamics New Video Presents Looming Possibilities</title>
        <description>&lt;h5 id=&quot;image-of-robot-atlas-was-taken-from-kansascitycom&quot;&gt;Image of Robot Atlas was taken from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kansascity.com/news/business/technology/917xpi/picture62197987/ALTERNATES/FREE_640/atlas%20from%20boston%20dynamics&quot;&gt;KansasCity.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yesterday, November 16, 2017, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostondynamics.com/&quot;&gt;Boston Dynamics&lt;/a&gt; released a video of their robot Atlas jumping onto platforms before finally performing a perfect backflip.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fRj34o4hN4I&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; gesture=&quot;media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &lt;p&gt;Boston Dynamics is a tech/engineering company headquartered in &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Waltham,_Massachusetts&quot;&gt;Waltham, Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt; with a focus on robotics with animal-like and human-like designs. Boston Dynamics’ robots have impressed many. They even caught Google’s eyes leading to Google X acquiring them in 2013 before eventually being sold to Japan’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SoftBank_Group&quot;&gt;SoftBank Group&lt;/a&gt;. They’ve also been known for some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v2-u0TZjuAk&quot;&gt;hilarious malfunctions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/boston-dynamics-flipping-robots/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/boston-dynamics-flipping-robots/</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transitioning Into A Tech Career</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Start with basic tech certifications such as the A+, find an area you are interested in, and then pursue it through self-study and certifications.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;my-story&quot;&gt;My Story&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;hr /&gt; &lt;p&gt;I started off my career working at restaurants. The very first job I had was cleaning at a seafood restaurant when I was in High School. My second job was as a cook at Steak n Shake, a popular burger joint. I hopped around from restaurant to restaurant as I was traveling. I was not sure what I wanted out of life at this point. One thing I was...</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/transitioning-to-a-tech-career/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/transitioning-to-a-tech-career/</guid>
        
        
        <category>advice</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
